New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, Environmental Conservation Division (PEF/ENCON); Records apap114
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1978-2000; 1; 7.2 cubic ft.
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1981 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1982 January-1982 June (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1982 July-1982 December (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1984 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, PEF Members, 1984-1988; 1990-1992; 1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Data Center Consolidation, 1995 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Day Care Services, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Deferred Compensation Plan, 1984; 1985; 1988; 1994 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Department of Civil Service, Abolished Positions Notice, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles Union Partnership Agreement, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Disability Leave, 1984 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Discipline Cases, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Diversity and Leadership Manuals, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Division 169, 1982-1984 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Division 169, 1986-1988; 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Division 169, 1995; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Division 169, Audit Committee Report, 1995 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Division 169, Constitution, 1981 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Division 169, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Division 169, Correspondence, 1980 January-1980 March (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Division 169, Correspondence, 1980 April; 1980 June-1980 July; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Division 169, Correspondence, 1980 August-1980 December (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Division 169, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1979-1982; 1990-1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Division 169, New Member Materials, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Division 169, Steward Elections, 1982; 1984; 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Division 169, Steward Handouts and Communications, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Division 169, Steward Handouts and Communications, 1981 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Division 169, Steward Handouts and Communications, 1982 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Division 169, Steward Handouts and Communications, 1982 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Division 169, Steward Handouts and Communications, 1983 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Division 169, Steward Meeting Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Division 169, Treasurers' Quarterly Reports, 1983-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Division 169, Treasurers' Quarterly Reports, 1990-2000 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Drug/Alcohol Testing Policies, 1986-1990 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Election, Campaigns, 1985 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Election, Campaigns, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Election, Campaigns, 1991; 1994 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Election, Candidate Rules and Petitions, 1985 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Election, Directory of Candidates and Campaign Statements, 1985; 1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Election, State-Wide, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Elections Committee and Position Vacancies, 1983-1988; 1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Employee Drug Testing, 1984 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Employee Organizational Leave Reimbursement, 1982-1984; 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act Liabilities, 1987-1988; 1992; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Ethics Code and Forms, 1988; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Ethics Grievances, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Executive Orders, 1984 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Existing Position Description, Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Films, Labor, 1981 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Financial Disclosure Act and Ethics Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Financial Disclosure Act and Ethics Legislation, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Financial Disclosure Act and Ethics Legislation, 1990; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Fiscal Policy Institute Briefing, 1996 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Flextime, 1983 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Galante, Peter, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - GOOD and Welfare, 1983-1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Grace, Thomas, 1985; 1990; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Graphic Communications International Union, 1987; 1991; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Green, Mark, Senate Campaign, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Grievances, Policies and Procedures, 1984; 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Harold, John, 1982; 1985 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Health and Safety Handbooks, Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Health Insurance, 1982-1990; 1992 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Health Insurance, 1993-1996; 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Health Insurance, COBRA, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Health Insurance, Community Health Plan, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Health Insurance, Domestic Partnerships, 1995 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Health Insurance, Empire Plan, 1985-1988; 1990; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Health Insurance, Empire Plan, Publications, 1986-1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Health Maintenance Organizations, 1985; 1986; 1988-1989; 1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Hoke, Elizabeth, 1982-1985 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Hotel, Motel, and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, 1983; 1986; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Improper Practice Charges, 1983; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Income Protection Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - "It's Our Money" Task Force Report on Pensions, 1990 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Keenan, Michael, Contract Grievance, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Kraemer, John, 1979; 1982-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 4 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - Landa, Irving, 1982-1985; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Layoffs, 1983; 1986 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Layoffs, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Layoffs, Information for Affected Members, 1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - League of Conservation Voters, National Environmental Scorecard, 1996 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Legal Appeals Procedures, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Legal Services, Reports, 1983-1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Agenda, 2000 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Letchworth Village Division, Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
    Conditions Governing Access
    This file is closed because the records fall under attorney/client privilege. A researcher must first obtain permission of the plaintiffs in order to view the file.
  - Litzenberger, Maggie, 1981; 1982; 1984; 1986-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Lobbying, Brochures, 1984; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Lockport Hospital Bargaining Unit, 1995 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Management/Confidential, 1984; 1986-1988; 1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Media Access Information, 1980; 1983; 1985; 1987; 1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Membership Benefits Fund, 1985; 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Membership Benefits Program, 1983; 1985; 1987-1988; 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Mental Hygiene Department, 1985 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - NDRI, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - New Member Kit, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - New York City Watershed Agreement, 1996 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1977-1979; 1980 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - New York State Assembly Standing Committee on Labor, Collective Bargaining System Report, 1984 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - New York State Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - New York State Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - New York State Constitution, 1976; 1978 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - New York State PEF, Annual Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - New York State PEF, Annual Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - New York State PEF, Annual Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - New York State PEF, Annual Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - New York State PEF, Clothing Catalog, Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - New York State PEF, Constitution and By-Laws, 1979-1980; 1983-1988; 1990 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - New York State PEF, Constitution and By-Laws, Drafts, 1979; 1982; 1988 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - New York State PEF, Constitution and Special Rules of Order, 1997 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - New York State PEF, Constitution, Proposed Amendments, 1984; 1988; 1997; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - New York State PEF, History, 1981; 1982 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - New York State PEF, Legal Counsel, 1982-1983 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - New York State PEF, Literature, 1979 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - New York State PEF, Organizational/Informational, 1980-1993; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - New York State PEF, Staff Assignments and Appointments, 1979-1994 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - New York State Public Employment Relations Board, Laws and Procedures, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - New York State United Teachers, 1979; 1981; 1982; 1984; 1996 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - New York State Workers' Compensation Manual, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Nuclear Freeze, 1985; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Nurse Teacher Proposed Resolution, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Nurses, 1985; Undated (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Occupational Accidents and Workers' Compensation Experiences for New York State Government Employees, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Office of Employee Relations, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Officer Elections, 1979 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1980 January-1980 February (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1980 March-1980 May (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1980 June-1980 July (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1980 August-1980 September (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1980 October-1980 December (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1981 January-1981 March (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1981 April-1981 December (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1982 January-1982 October (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1982 November-1982 December (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Officers, Leadership, and Executive Board, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Officers and Staff Meetings, Minutes and Notes, 1982 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Officers Meetings, 1983-1984; 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - OMRDD / OMH, 1981-1984; 1986 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Oral Exams, Handbooks, 1984; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Out-of-Title Court Victory, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - PS&T United, 1979-1982; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary Procedure and Collective Bargaining Information, Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Part Time/Shared Job Project, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Participation by Agency Report, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Participation by Region, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Pataki, George, 1994-1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Pension Supplementation, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Performance Advance/Evaluation System, 1980-1981 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Performance Advance/Evaluation System, 1983-1984 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Phone and Mail Lists, 1979-1984 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Phone and Mail Lists, 1985-1988; 1991-1995; 1998-1999 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Policy, Correspondence, 1986; 1988-1989 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Policy Manual, Affirmative Action, 1981; 1985; 1991; 1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Policy Manual, Benefits, 1980; 1982; 1987; 1989; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Policy Manual, Civil Service Issues, 1979; 1989; 1990; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Policy Manual, Committees, 1980; 1985; 1988-1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Policy Manual, Contract, 1984-1985; 1987-1989; 1993; 1995-1996; 1998 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Policy Manual, Convention, 1980-1982; 1984; 1989; 1991; 1994 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Policy Manual, Divisions, 1981-1988; 1990-1991; 1993; 1998 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Policy Manual, Elections, 1980-1984; 1987-1989; 1994; 1997; 2000 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Policy Manual, Executive Board, 1980-2000 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Policy Manual, Finance, 1980-1985; 1987-1994; 1997; 1999 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Policy Manual, Internationals, 1980; 1982; 1986; 1987 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Policy Manual, Labor Organizations, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Policy Manual, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Policy Manual, PEF Staff, 1982-1983; 1985-1988; 1992-1993; 1995; 1998 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Policy Manual, Political Action, 1981-1988; 1990-1991; 1994-1996; 1998-1999 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Policy Manual, Publications, 1981; 1989-1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Policy Manual, Table of Contents, 1999; 2000 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1979-1984 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Privacy Policy, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Privatization Articles, 1988 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Professional Licensing Revisions, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Professional, Scientific, and Technical Unit Election, CSEA Challenge, 1978 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Program for the 1980s for Effective Membership Services (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Proskin, Arnold and Croak, Richard, Political Campaigns, 1984-1988 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Proskin v. Croak, Slander Lawsuit, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Public Employees Benefit Fund, 1983; 1986-1990; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - Reductions in Force, 1982; 1984 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - Retirees, Region 8, 1983-1984; 1986; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - Retirees, Statewide, 1981; 1984-1985; 1987-1988; 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)
  - Retirement Brochures, General, 1982-1987; 1997; 2000 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - Retirement Incentive Program, 1983; 1987 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 54)
  - Retirement Incentive Program, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 55)
  - Retirement Incentive Program, 1991; 1995; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 56)
  - Retirement Laws, New York State, 1987-1989; 1993; 1995; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 57)
  - Retirement Plan, Benefits, 2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 58)
  - Retirement Plan, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1977; 1983-1989; 1991-1994; 1996-2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 59)
  - Retirement Plan, Tier 1 and 2, Brochures, 1977; 1981-1983; 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 60)
  - Retirement Plan, Tier 3 and 4, Brochures, 1983-1984; 1986; 1989; 1991; 1997-1999 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 61)
  - Retirement Plan, Tiers 1-4, Correspondence, News Clippings, and Manuals, 1976; 1983; 1986 (Box 6 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 62)
  - Right to Know Law, 1980; 1983; 1985-1988; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Roswell Park Scientist Promotion Review and Reclassification, 1982; 1985-1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Roswell Park Scientist Promotion Review and Reclassification, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Roswell Park Steward Election Lawsuit, 1986-1987 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Sano, Joseph, 1983-1984; 1988 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Sano, Josephine, 1987; 2001 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Satz, Jeffrey, 1982-1983; 1986-1987 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Schafer, Howard, 1981; 1988-1991 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Schafer, Howard, 1992-1994; 1999; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Programs, 1987; 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Secretary/Treasurer Directives, 1984; 1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Security Unit Employees Council 82, Contract, 1982-1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Service Employees International Union, 1984-1986; 1988-1990; 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Service Employees International Union, Constitutions, 1976; 1984 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Service Employees International Union/PEF Hearing, Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Service Employees International Union Local 200, Constitution, 1979 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Sexual Orientation, Non-Discrimination Policy, 1984 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Sheedy, James, Award Dinner, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Shop Talk, Correspondence, 1985; 1992 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Shop Talk, Working File, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Sierra Club, Hudson-Mohawk Group, Atlantic Chapter, 1982-1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Snow Emergency, Attendance Issues, 1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Social Security Brochures, 1981; 1982; 1988; 1990; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1984-1990 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Statewide Governor Election, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Steward Manual, 1978; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Steward Manual, First Draft, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Steward Manual, First Draft, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Steward Manual, Front Matter, 1985; 1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Steward Manual, Inserts, 1985; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Steward Manual, Section 1, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Steward Manual, Sections 2-4, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Steward Manual, Sections 6-10, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Steward Manual, Sections 11-14, 1985 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Steward Training, 1979; 1981; 1983-1984; 1991; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Steward Training, Labor/Management Workshop, Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Student Financial Aid Guide, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Taxation of Benefits, 1988 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Taylor Law, 1979-2000 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Taylor Law, Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Telephone Directory, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Tonko, Paul, 1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Townsend, John, 1986 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Transition Report, 1991 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Transition Report for Governor-Elect Pataki, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Transportation Bond Issue, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Trustees, Correspondence and Reports, 1979-1982; 1984-1989; 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Tuition Reimbursement, 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Tuition Tax Credits, 1982 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Handbooks, 1979-1980; 1983-1984; 1986; 1992-1993 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - U.S. Savings Bonds, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - Unemployment Insurance, Information for Claimants, 1982 (Box 7 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)